One of my hobbies is I collect dust.
Are you from this country?
I go around town slashing tire prices.
Do you get that?
Do you know that Christmas song, Do you
hear what I hear? Do you
You stop laughing. You stop laughing,
sir. You got the idea. There are no
jokes.
There's a kind of hush all over this
room.
I'm addicted to prescription glasses
and 2020 wants to do my life story.
It gets where a four-year-old wrote
this.
>> Thank you. No, I'm not leaving yet. Hold
on.
This is my step ladder. I never knew my
real ladder.
I heard great things about my real
ladder. That he supported three people
at one time.
The last I heard he's one I [__] that
up, too.
The last I heard he was in the 12step
program.
It really didn't matter. Oh, thank you.
>> Play football. I was a setback.
Anyway, I've had a lovely That's it for
me. Thank you very much. Thank you very
much.
Anyway, with that, I'm going to bring up
the man. Do you know the man? Mr. Who?
Mr. Lou. Who? What? Mr. Louis Prima. No.
Mr. Louis Armstrong. No. Mr. Louis CK.
Here he is.
Oh my god, you guys. Oh my god. Thank
you.
This you guys you guys did great. Thank
This is what I talk like now. Just so
you know.
I'm going to do the whole show like
this.
Really a very offensive stereotype
of a Mexican.
This is
This is a Mexican at the border. Just
let me in.
Jesus.
He won't. You guys are dicks in there
anyway.
[__] you, America.
Is that too high up, do you think?
So I like I always like to stand just a
little bit wrong, you know, just for my
own entertainment instead of standing
like this. Just put it a little bit up
here just so people are like I don't I
don't know why that bothers me.
Especially if I'm somewhere I don't like
being like CVS, you know? I hate CVS,
but sometimes you got to go in there.
That should be their slogan. CVS.
CVS. Sometimes you got to come in here
or else you got to get your wart
band-aids
and that's stuff for your dry vagina.
Dry vaginer.
I used to think it was uh called a
vagin.
I did because I grew up in Boston
and the I don't know if you are familiar
with people call it the Boston accent.
It's not an accent. It's a whole city of
people saying most words wrong.
It's just stupidity in a massive region
because my teachers they teach you to
talk like that. My teacher miss I had a
teacher named Miss Dory but she thought
her name was Mrs. Darity.
She mispronounced her own name,
Mity.
And she gave us she gave us sex head.
This was fifth grade. We had sex head
with Mrs. Darity. And she's showing us
the diagram. She's like, "This is a
penis
and this is a vagina."
Now during intercourse, the man
ejaculates sperm
up into the vagina.
And then later
a [__] baby
comes out of the vagina.
Sometimes it's [__]
This was the 70s. She used a teacher
said [__] in Boston in the 70s.
My daughter's [__] She used to tell
us every day, I have a daughter and
she's mentally [__]
She's 35 and she lives in my house.
She better be [__] [__]
I'm going to stick her back up in my
vagina.
So, I thought it was called a vagin till
I was like 25. And I remember thinking
it was like a it's a vagin. It's a like
a thing
that vagines,
you know.
Like you use it to vag I got to vagine
my driveway. I don't know. Like
just got to vagine this new table I just
made.
That would make a nice table. Like you
make a new table and then you take the
80 grit paper and you sand it and then
120 and then you go, "All right, honey.
Get up there." And she just
it's like old like one of those Danish
tables or like a
ooh nice old Italian table.
This table is a very smooth because uh
my wife have a very juy boozy and she
vagina the table
and my family we do this for generations
and we vagine
All right.
So, I'm 47 now and uh yeah, I know
that's about what it's worth.
That's what that's what that deserves.
Yeah. 47 doesn't buy anything. 18 you
can vote. 21 you can drink. And 47, you
can just just keep doing whatever. Just
do
keep being out of breath.
One good thing is that I've let go of
any dream of getting in great shape.
Like it's like a relief
just cuz my whole life I've been like,
"Well, at someday I should really get in
great shape." Now I'm like, "What? Why
would I do that? That's not going to
happen." just to me the bar the level I
want to reach as far as the shape I'm
in. I just want it to be so that if you
find out that I died, you ask what
happened. That's all
I want you to wonder what happened.
I don't want to be like, "Oh, he died."
Oh, yeah. Sure. Sure he did. Sure he
did.
To be a bigger news. Did you hear Louis
still alive? [__] Oh, really? Oh my
god.
Oh my god. How?
How?
Something's changed when you get older.
Like I've reallocated some of the noises
that I make.
Like the noise I used to make when I
come is now the noise I make when I pee.
Oh,
take it all, [__]
Very disrespectful to my toilet,
unfortunately.
>> Yeah, you like that piss, don't you,
[__]
I'm going to [__] in your mouth, too,
cuz you ain't None but a shitty piss
drinking telly.
Dumb [__] tell it. You ain't
intelligent.
You ain't even been outside.
Sit there waiting for me to [__] in your
face.
Got piss on your lips.
You ain't even special. I pissed in
three toilets today.
You ain't [__]
It's terrible.
It's awful.
But that's how my dad treated his
toilet. So that's where I learned it.
It's a shame.
So that's the noise I make when I pee.
And uh some of you might be wonder, none
of you are wondering,
what noise do I make when I come? So
this is the noise I make when I come. I
just go. It is done.
Thing with clouds and lightning and
crows. The circle is complete.
Kind of intense.
There's a little witch with white eyes
going and the child would be born. And I
don't know.
One time I was having sex with a woman.
It was our first time having sex. Also
turned out to be our last time. Uh but I
wasn't didn't know that.
Anyway, I was getting I was going to
come soon. So I felt like talking about
it and but I didn't know her very well.
So it came out weird. I said, "Oh, I'm
coming."
She's like, "What did you say?
Cuz
I was back there. That's why That's why
she had to go like this. What' you say?
What was that back there, Chief? What
was that?
>> Cuz I'm always back there.
It's a It's a weird thing to brag about.
I'm always behind them every time.
so they don't see me crying.
It's weird having sex with a woman from
behind because you don't know what's
going on the whole time. I get kind of
paranoid.
You know, the whole time she might be
like
I was on the subway in New York. Uh,
this isn't another sex story.
This is a traveling story.
Like, you ready?
So, I'm on the subway and I'm standing
there. I wasn't holding anything. I just
like to stand like this. I'm standing
there.
I walk around the city like this. Hi.
So, I'm standing there and from behind
me over here, I hear this. I hear
and I was like, "Oo, okay. There's a
crazy person." I mean, it's not a big
surprise in New York. Then I heard it
again. I was like, "All right, I want to
see. I want to see the crazy person.
Just want to take a look." So, I look
over and it's not what I expected. It
wasn't a big homeless guy with two sets
of headphones that don't work or
anything like that. It was a
a young woman. She looked like she was
about 21. And she's standing there.
She's very kind of nice, properly
dressed. She was very like Michigany or
something. Very suburban Michigany kind
of thing. And she's standing there with
a ponytail. And then all of a sudden she
starts going like this. She goes la.
and I realized, oh, she's like a
student, like a singing music student,
and she's doing her vocal exercises on
the subway. You know what? It wasn't
charming
or nice. It was arrogant and rude cuz
she just had this look like, it's I'm so
cool cuz I'm studying music in New York
City and I just do my thing right on the
subway every day.
La
everybody.
tired nurse who just did a 14-our shift.
We live in an interesting time. You
know, cuz you can be on an airplane,
you're like one of 200 passengers.
You're on a flight 30,000 ft in the air
in the middle of the flight. If you just
decide to do this, you're sitting in
your seat and you just start going like
this. You go.
If you do that and don't stop doing it,
they will land the plane.
You can will a plane to the ground
without a weapon or a threat.
You don't even have to do that much. You
can just sit there and just start going
down,
down.
Seriously, if you were on a plane and
you just didn't stop saying down, down,
down.
Sir, is there a problem? Down.
Down.
Fighter jets will appear. I mean, you'll
go into the nearest airport.
And then I guess you're in trouble. But
what? They can't put you like in prison
cuz you said down several times.
They'd like bother you. Why'd you do Are
you a terrorist? Why'd you do it? I just
didn't want to be up anymore. Just
didn't like it. I mean, I just said the
word of the where I wanted to be.
You didn't have to do it.
It's just suggestion. Jesus Christ.
I was on a plane once and there was two
babies on a plane and other people.
Wasn't just
Wasn't just me and two babies.
That would be weird.
You get on a plane, there's just two
babies.
Come on, we're leaving soon.
He's the pilot baby.
I'm the other baby.
No, it's all right. I'm not going to.
You babies have a good flight, but I'm
going to find another way to get there.
Yeah. I don't like the way this was
starting.
Anyway, I was on a plane and there was
uh these two babies and they're crying
the whole time. Crying the whole flight
and that happens a lot. I don't think
they knew each other. They're just
crying.
I've seen this on so many flights. I
started to wonder, is there a reason for
this? Is there like an actual reason why
babies? So, I looked it up. Turns out
there's an actual reason why babies cry
on airplanes and it's because they're
upset that gay people are getting
married.
Yeah.
Like really upset. like inconsolably
upset.
Honey, it's the country's changing.
And I don't agree with him. I think if
people are in love, they should get
married. But they can't these they can't
accept that
cuz they're just, you know, they're just
being babies.
Babies are selfish.
They are. Babies are selfish. Please me.
No baby ever goes, "How are you doing
though?"
I have two daughters and both of them at
one time were babies and I held them and
they cried on planes. It's happened to
me. I've had a baby on a plane. If
you're ever, this is how selfish people
are. When you're on a plane and you hear
a baby crying, you think that's
happening to you. You're like, "This is
going to ruin my flight. It's going to
ruin it."
Well, look at the parent cuz that person
is holding a crying baby on a plane,
which means they've been traveling with
a baby all day, which means they have a
baby.
Okay? So, their life isn't even good.
They don't like anything. Their whole
life is h Jesus.
If there's any joy for them, it's that
this is now bothering other people.
Yeah, you listen to this [__] now. Wang.
I remember one time my babe was crying
on the plane. She was really upset and
this guy and some businessman on the
plane cuz businessmen always think that
every flight is a private plane of
theirs
that we're all like piggybacking on.
And this guy has his [__] newspaper
and he turns around and look at me and
my baby and he looks right at me. He
doesn't kind of like go like this. He
looks at me like, "Hm."
Like, "Could you
like Oh, I'm sorry. Is this bothering
you? Let me just
You all just clap for a dead baby.
You applauded a dead baby.
I have two uh children
uh nine and 12 years old. Both girls. Uh
they're both gay.
Um,
I'm raising them gay.
Most people raise their kids straight.
I'm just going to raise mine gay.
They'll do what they want later, but uh,
as long as they're in my house, they're
gay.
I tell them every day, "You're gay,
honey. Good night.
Go to bed. Brush your gay teeth, gay,
honey.
Don't forget to be gay.
Having children is a big responsibility.
And I've never really done very well at
it. I've made a lot of mistakes. Some of
them big, some of them small. You know,
like I'm still a person. I still I'm an
idiot, you know. Still like I I want I
got high one night. I got really high
because I don't do drugs. I never do
drugs. Never. so that when I do,
they're way more fun.
To me, that's my best advice about drug.
If you want to enjoy drugs, never do
them. Never. Because then when you do,
they're actually fun. Cuz when drugs are
part of your life, they're just another
pain in the ass in your life. It's just
an ah my drug suck. I don't want to have
that problem.
I always want to be that person where
it's a new thing. Somebody's like, "Hey,
you want to try this?" And I'm like,
"Oh, I don't know. I should. It's crazy.
I don't even know how to do it. I mean,
what is this?"
Anyway, I got my my friend had the
little a vape. I'm a little worried
honestly by the young people with the
vaping and the they just do this and
then they just vape and they just stand
on the corner and puff and look at the
[__] thing. And I miss I miss you. I
that's what it is. I miss you people cuz
you used to stand around like this and I
get to go [__] that one and that was
okay. But now I don't even I'm just
looking at the top of people's heads
now. But I didn't realize how like my
friend I have a younger friend who vapes
and she told me it's just to kind of
like calm down. And she's like, I barely
feel it. You know, sometimes it helps me
sleep. So, one night we're hanging out.
I'm like, I'm going to go home and go to
sleep. Let me try it. So, I took one
little tiny hit. I was I was insane. I
was completely insane. I was in my
house. I couldn't even walk past the
window. I had to go under the windows
cuz I was afraid of the inside of my own
brain.
So, I started texting people. Just being
just texting. I'm so high. I'm so
[__] high. I'm so high. I tested, you
know, another friend. I'm so high. I
want to suck the pot jizz out of my own
dick and get higher. That's what I
wrote. I'm not bragging. I'm just
telling you that's what I wrote. And I
sent it.
And then later, I looked at my text and
I was like, I think I might have sent
that to my 12-year-old daughter. I think
it's possible.
And I didn't, but I too easily could
have. We need There Now my kids are in
my phone. There needs to be a some very
reliable firewall
that says these numbers are much harder
to text that you can't just whoops
traumatized her reversibly
that you can go like I to write to these
numbers I have to solve the Hellraiser
puzzle and I have to there's two guys
with the keys the opposite room that
turn them at the same moment
and there's a warning.
Are you sure you want to send this
picture of your pubic hair
to your exwife's mother?
That's how you want to break the
silence. 6 years since the divorce.
This is my pubic hair. Look at all of my
pubic hair. How have you been?
I try to be a good dad, but you know,
like the life just kind of takes off.
Your kids start, you know, they get
their own ideas and their My 9-year-old,
she's just figuring out about lying, and
that's a tough thing. It's hard to roll
that one back because lying is pretty
amazingly useful in life. It's like, how
do you tell a kid not to use a thing
that just solves every possible problem?
Like magic.
How do you
Cuz that's why kids lie cuz they're in
trouble. They lie cuz they're in more
trouble than they can take. You know,
cuz kids 9-year-old when a nine-year-old
lies, it's not for some weird
machavellian, you know? Do you know what
my teacher said about you? It's
interesting. They don't just make [__]
up.
They lie because they're in trouble. And
it's more than naked cuz trouble is too
much for a kid. Trouble for grown-ups,
we can take trouble. We don't care. We
just go, "Oh, I'm sorry.
Am I in trouble?
Oh, whoops."
We don't care.
But to a little kid, trouble is like
this horrible. Did you take the
chocolate?
And she did. And she doesn't know how to
handle it. Did you Did you take it?
No.
Well, all right then. Have a nice day.
How do you then tell her, "Yeah, don't
ever apply that perfect solution again
to terrifying things."
Mark Twain once said, "A man who always
tells the truth doesn't have to remember
what he said, and that's great." But
Mark Twain also said, "There once was a
big black guy named [__] Jim." So,
I don't know if
100% of the things he said
were perfectly awesome.
Really, Mark? [__] Jim, you're going
to go with That's the best you could do
to name the Yeah, kind of a nice ring to
it. [__] Jim. Yeah. Well, it's a
little on the nose, isn't it?
Could have called him Black Mike. I
mean, just a little take it down one
notch of the Thanks for that, Mark.
Anyway,
so while we're in this area,
now that I know you guys are cool, no,
no. Um, no, no, but uh but uh but but
this is a story that takes place. I'm
going to tell you the story. It's kind
of a messy story. It takes place over a
lot of years cuz it start it started
with my friend Mike who told me the
story. This happened to him back in the
'9s. Uh he was going home for Christmas
and uh he lives in Connecticut. He grew
up in Connecticut in some shitty [__]
town in shitty shitty Connecticut and he
didn't like going home. He's one of
those people. He came from a place he
doesn't like it anymore. And he goes
back. He doesn't know how to handle his
family, you know, and he came from a
family of white racists and he doesn't
like going home, but it's still home. So
he went home for Christmas one year and
everybody's hanging out during the day
talking, having lunch, and his father
and his brother both work at this
factory and his brother's grousing about
his day at work and he goes, "Yeah." And
then this [__] [__] fell asleep
with a forklift. And then my my friend
Mike heard that and he went, "Oh god,
why? Why am I part of this people? I
hate this." And he felt bad. And then
that night he's in the kitchen and he's
having a warm milk or whatever. And he I
don't know why that's I don't know why
that's funny, but what that says about
Yeah, cuz he's a [__] No, he's just
sort of having some time to himself and
his cousin comes downstairs with staying
and his cousin, he likes his cousin. And
that's the one person he always felt
connected with. And his cousin's like,
"What's wrong, man?" And he says, "Well,
jeez. I come home and I hoped that
everything would be, you know, normal."
But then my brother says, "Oh, he's
about the factory and this [__] fell
asleep with the forklift." And his
cousin goes, "Oh my god, the [__] fell
asleep with the forklift."
So, this is the first part of the story.
Okay, so Mike tells me that story about
how he's just not listened to by anybody
in his family. And then later on I get a
job writing on a TV show for Cedric the
Entertainer. Great guy. And he had a
show and he hired a writing staff, half
white writers, half black writers. So at
lunchtime we talked about race. It was
just a we'd have these provocative
interesting conversations trading notes
about race, the white writers and the
black writers. And I told that story. I
told the whole thing about the guy
[__] the for and then the cousin
saying for and then one of the writers,
a black writer, he goes, "There's
nothing worse than a [__] fall asleep
in the forklift.
making it harder for the rest of us.
Still,
nobody's quite hearing what my friend
was going through.
And then
about a year later, I'm hanging out with
my friend Dino. Dino's Greek. He has no
dog in the race. He doesn't care either
way. He's Greek. Greeks aren't white or
black. They're just he's just got a big
nose and he just stands there.
I told Dino the whole story. I told him
about the guy the forklift and the and
then the black
and then Dino says, "How do you fall
asleep at a forklift?
My oldest daughter is going to be 13
next year. That's a big deal. That's a
big deal. That's all the parents ahead
of you always going.
You wait till she
that's when you
I'm not afraid of her teenagehood. It's
going to be challenging and difficult
and she'll meet the challenges. You
know, I'm always proud of my kid. She's
a good kid. Now, some parents are really
afraid of their daughters. A lot of dads
get scared like I don't know what to do.
I have this friend. His daughter's 15.
And he's like, "She's going to start
having sex. I don't know what to do.
She's going to have sex. What do I do?"
I'm like, "Well, you don't do anything.
You don't have a role in that at all.
You're her the father. No role. Not
supportive or advisory. Nothing."
But what if she has a bad sexual
experience? Oh, she's going to have a
number of those. Oh, yes, she is. Her
whole life is going to be just walking
through a blizzard of bad dicks. Just
dicks. Just Jesus. What the [__] That
was a big one. Holy [__] I'm just
trying to get to work.
the little one, the nine-year-old,
life's a little simpler. Tap dancing.
She takes tap dancing class. Uh we
started her with tap dancing because we
figure by the time she grows up it'll be
the 1930s again. And uh yeah, she'll
have this thing she can do that nobody
enjoys watching.
Do you know who the audience is for tap
dancing? The parents of tap dancing
students. That's all of it. because we
all have to go to the show at the end of
the tap dancing semester
and they have a big theater show and all
the kids get up there, they all tap
dance in groups of threes.
There's about 6,000 kids.
They do about 20 minutes each. So, the
show's about 7 months long and everybody
dies at the end,
but you go because you want to see your
kid tap dance cuz that's an amazing
thing because this was a baby. She was
just a baby. She was just like,
"That's it." And now she's going like
this.
It's amazing.
But you got to watch all those other
kids that you don't love at all.
You got to watch people grown-ups do it.
There's grownup adult students and they
get up there. Get off. Nobody's here to
see you. Nobody. Your parents are dead.
You're 52.
Nobody came from work. Nobody came from
work.
I take her every uh every Thursday to
tap dancing. And we go up to the to the
school and uh she puts on her tap shoes
and she goes in the room. I don't go in
there and she tap dances and I wait
outside because it's 40 minutes. It's
not enough time to go anywhere. So I
just sit there and listen to
And she comes out. I'm tired of this. I
don't want to go anymore. Good. Don't. I
don't want to bring you. Quit. Quit.
I don't care. I don't push my kids into
this [__] Cuz you got to do it, too. I
don't want to do it,
Daddy. I'm tired of soccer. Soccer is
out of our lives forever
with those words from thine mouth.
Soccer is gone. I don't care. Don't go
to school. I don't want to get up at
7:00.
Don't do any of this [__] honey. I
don't care. I have money. Just eat the
food in the house.
Stay home and eat.
You and your sister don't have kids. I
can cover all of us and then we all die.
That's my goal. I want to make enough
money that we could just lock the door
and eat the food.
That's it.
Daddy, what are we doing today? Go to
the food room and pick something out and
go to bed.
That's all that's required of you.
People People overthink this life [__]
People get all knotted up. I don't know
what to do with my life. Like I don't
know like what I should be or like I
don't know. saying, "What should I like
do with my with like my life?
Just get food. Put it in the Put food in
here. That's it. Put food in here. Walk
around and look for food.
And anytime you see any food, put it in
here. Just take it and put it in here.
Later, when you feel pressure, [__] out
the [__] in there.
That's it. If anybody tries to stop you
from doing either of those, murder them.
That's it.
Doesn't have to be more complicated.
Do it till you're died. Till you're
dead. Till you're dead. Died. Dead.
I don't know how long I'm going to live.
I have no idea. You don't really ever
get to find out.
You never get to go, "Okay, I'm dead."
So, 80.
You don't ever get to have that thought.
This is it. You get to go, "This is
probably it." That's That's your last
thought. This is probably it right here.
Yeah. Well, we're all going to die at
some point. It's true, man. And you find
out at some point. It's an interesting
thing about human beings that we live
with the knowledge that we're going to
die. I found out when I was seven that
everybody dies. My grandfather told me,
he said, "Everybody dies."
I wasn't even talking to him.
I was just trying to blow out the
candles.
Now, I was 7 years old when I found out
that everybody dies. And I was excited,
not cuz everybody dies, but cuz I knew
it. I was excited cuz I knew I was young
to know that everybody dies. I knew that
most of my friends didn't know. And I
thought, I want to tell them. I want to
be the one that tells everybody. I
especially wanted to tell Benji, this
kid across the street from me. There's
this kid, Benji. He I didn't He wasn't
my friend. I was seven and he was six,
but if I ever came out in my front yard,
he would come out and I'd be like, "Oh,
here here he comes."
Just hated him. Hated him. first person
I ever hated. Like visceral hate. He was
to me he was a piece of [__] [__]
[__] That's what he was to me. And I
didn't even know any of those words. I
just had that like as a raw feeling with
no way to say it. I was too young for
the feeling that I had. And then
somebody I heard somebody say piece of
[__] [__] [__] I was like,
"Dad, yes. Thank you." That's what that
Yes. That's how Yes.
Anyway, one day I was in my front yard
and piece of [__] Benji comes across
and he says, "I got a new bike or
something like that and I was like, uh,
you're going to die someday."
He was like, "What? No, I'm not." I
said, "Yes, you are. Everybody dies.
You're gonna die and your mom's gonna
die
and your daddy's gonna die
in that order.
He's really upset and he starts running.
It's still funny to me. It still makes
me laugh 40 years later. I can still see
it so clearly and it still makes me
laugh. Run, Benji.
You can't run from this [__] [__]
Is it going to get you?
Wonder if he's dead.
Anyway,
so he came back with his mom. His mom's
so angry. And then I was scared and his
mom came over. What did you say to him?
And I said, I I told him that everybody
dies.
And she goes, well, that's not
necessarily true.
I was like, "What?" She says, "Well,
some people die, but not everybody
does."
And I was so full of questions. I was
like, "What about what about Abraham
Lincoln and George Washington? They're
dead." But she said, "Yeah, that's cuz
something happened to them. George
Washington didn't take care of himself
and Lincoln got shot, but there's a lot
of people alive from those days." And I
was like, "Really?
what about like Bible people? And she's
like, "Yeah, I we have to go." And then
she left cuz I think she realized this
is only going to get worse. She's not on
a good side of this argument.
And then I went to my mom. I told the
whole thing. She was like, "Don't worry.
That lady's a [__] idiot. Don't
listen to her."
My mom said, "Don't worry, baby. You're
definitely going to die.
Mhm.
People from the Bible.
I wonder if people in the Bible knew
they were going to be in the Bible. Like
you guys, this is totally going to be in
the Bible. This is to You guys are going
to get in the Bible. Everybody,
I got to get my roots done so I look
good for the Bible.
Yeah, my uh my dog died recently. I had
to tell the kids that the dog is dead.
That's a tough thing, telling your kids
that the dog died. You got to tell them
at some point. You can't just keep
going. Where? No, he's Where'd he go?
Oh, there he goes. I don't know. He's
that little scamp.
Go get him.
told my kids the dog died and we dealt
with it. And I was proud of them how
they expressed their feelings about it.
They cried. I was proud of them how they
dealt with their feelings and what they
said about it and how they processed.
And I realized this was a positive
thing. That's how you start thinking as
a parent. A lot of things you don't
think of would be positive really are
cuz you cuz a dog dying is an
opportunity to deal with death with your
kids. It's like a dry run for grandma.
It is. It is.
dog dies, you talk about it, you deal
with it. Later on, you go, "So, you know
all that stuff we talked about about the
dog?" Yes. So, grandma now.
Mhm.
All the same stuff. That's right.
All right. Go brush your teeth.
I had a dog when I was a kid and he
hated me. And it really hurt. It's true
story. My dog hated me. And I I wanted a
dog so bad. I was like 10 years old. I
used to beg my mother for a dog. And she
just would say like, "You had one when
you're a baby and it died. It's fine."
But finally, she said, "You can have a
dog if you keep your room clean for a
month." And I was so excited cuz I was
like, "I'm getting a dog." I told all my
friends, "I'm going to get a dog. All I
have to do is keep my room clean for a
month." I lasted about a week and it
just went to [__] I couldn't do it. And
I tried like 3 4 days. I couldn't do it.
And I got so depressed. I was like, "I'm
10 and I already know my life is going
to be [__] cuz I can't do anything."
And finally my mom was like, "Just well,
get the dog. You're buming everybody
out."
So she got us a dog. And the dog looked
at me and he hated me on site and I
worked hard to take care of this dog. I
was kind to him and he still hated me,
which hurt. That's why it hurt cuz he
must have just hated like who I am
inside.
He you could tell how he felt cuz he was
very expressive. He was a terrier, you
know, so he had eyebrows.
Like I'd walk in the room and he'd go
like, "Oh, [__] I can't." And he would
just leave.
I would take him for a walk and I had to
use a leash. And I didn't want to use a
leash. I want to be one of those cool
guys with a dog that just comes along.
You know those guys always got like a
suede jacket with patches in it and like
scratchy hair and he's like, "Hey." and
gets in his old pickup and he's like,
"Come on, D." He goes like, you know
those guys that can whistle, that cool
whistle,
whatever.
And the dog jumps in the back and they
both get laid somewhere because they're
both so cool. That's what I wanted.
But my dog, we go for a walk and the
leash was like taught like this. It
wasn't even like, "Yeah, we're friends."
It was like, "Dude, how far from this
kid can I get my face?" He would be
choking himself the whole
And if I ever like slipped and dropped
the leash, he he was like, "I'm not your
dog." He would just run. He would run
like a slave. He would just take off.
That's how we ran. It's an app
description.
It's how he ran. He didn't run like a
deer. This is how deer. He ran like
this.
He ran away so many times and then we
got a call from the pound. Hi, we have
your dog. And you could hear my dog in
the background like, don't
seriously,
I told you I don't want to
I never been a big uh animal person. I
don't Some animals I hate. Uh bats. I
think bats are just disgusting. I hate
bats. I hate It's a rat with leather
wings. You ever seen one and they like
look around? It's like somebody, you
know, they have a face. It's disgusting.
Hate bats. And I'm sure there's a whole
thing of, "Oh, did you know that bats
make all the French toast in the world
or whatever?
I don't care.
Hate them.
Had a bad bad experience
this summer. I was We rented a house
this summer. I got a house for me and
the kids. My ex-wife and I, we share
custody of the kids. So, the summer half
one month they go with her, one month
with me. So, I got a nice house in the
country and it was beautiful. The kids
loved it. But the kids go to sleep at,
you know, 8:00 at night. So, I'm just
laying awake.
Terrified.
Terrified. I'm so scared in the country
cuz it's just quiet and it's just
mystery and trees and darkness. I live
in New York City. I feel perfectly safe
there. I'm surrounded by murderers and
child molesters and Jews.
All right. I mean, there are there are a
lot there's a bunch of those. But so
so one night I'm in the country house
and I'm just laying just laying awake
just begging for the [__] sun to come
up so I can sleep through my days with
the kids.
And I'm laying awake and I'm my my
bedroom's above the kitchen and I
suddenly I hear this. I swear to God I
heard this sound. And I heard, "Why are
you singing?"
I heard that like clear as a bell. And
immediately my heart is pound. I'm like,
I'm going to have a heart attack right
now because there is a witch in the
kitchen.
First of all, there are witches. I have
no doubt in that moment. There's
witches. That's how easy it was to flip
me over. There witches.
And there's one in the kitchen. And I
got to go down there. I got to I can't
just She'll get They like kids that
she'll get the kids.
So I go downstairs. I'm terrified.
And I'm standing outside the kitchen
door like this for like an hour, too
scared to go in until I little bit of
logic seeped in and told me even if
there is a witch in there, she wouldn't
just make a noise and then just stand
there for like an hour.
So I go in, there's nobody in the
kitchen. And then I hear the noise
again. And it was the dishwasher. The
dishwasher has weird tubes and when the
soap goes through them, it's kind of
vocal. I don't know why, but it goes.
It was the weirdest thing to watch my
dishwasher do it. I was like, "All
right, it's cool. I'm fine. There's no
witches.
I'm about to go upstairs and a and a
bat, a [__] [__] bat
picked that." He's like, and he just
flew right right by my head like this
and I just I went and I just fell on the
floor
and I immediately I crawled into the
closet. I closed the door and I called
911 right away.
I don't know if you ever called 911 and
you don't realize till they answer how
you shouldn't be calling 911.
911, tell us your emergency. I I'm
sorry. I'm very sorry to be bothering
you. This doesn't qualify.
Lady's like, "Sir, what's the problem?"
I said, "There's a bat in my house
and I don't like it."
She was nice to me cuz it's country 911.
If you call 911 in New York City, this
is bad in my house. They'll be like,
"Sir, we'll send a car right over to
shoot you in the face."
But she's she was nice. She's like,
"Sir, we understand you're divorced.
You're overcompensating with a country
house. You're in over your head."
She said, "Call this guy." She gave me a
number. She said, "Call this guy. He's
he's a guy who takes care of bats. He's
a man who's uh bats are his focus." Felt
like she was doing a lot of work to not
say Batman. Like she was kind of going
around. He's a male human who bats are
his I'm not gonna say bat. I don't want
to say it.
So I call the Batman
and he comes over and I'm in the closet
looking through the crack and the bat is
on the ceiling hanging upside down. He's
just looking around.
It's the most disgusting thing.
And so finally there's a knock at my
door and I go and I crawl to the door
and I open it and he's like hello
and he says, "Where's the bat?" And I'm
like,
so the guy walks over
and he just takes the bat.
That's it.
He just took it.
He's like, "All right."
Like, "Yeah, you pretty much nailed it.
That's amazing."
It's like I called somebody and said,
"Help. There's a box of tissues on my
table."
Oh, thank goodness.
What a relief to have a man in the
house.
Would you like some sweet tea?
Wasn't expecting company.
Oh, my robe fell open.
He saw my breasts.
Ooh, what do we do now,
Mr. Batman?
You know, I'm kind of grateful to that
bat now.
Now that you're going to [__] me.
You're not.
Well, all right. You can go then.
I can't I can't get out of it.
I'm sorry.
All right. I just like to keep doing
that till the laughter stops.
Just [__] He's really This is getting
upsetting. What if I just did that for
like 40 minutes? Well, if you weren't
going to help me, then why did you come
over?
I'm alone here all day and I hardly can
handle it anymore.
All right. Okay.
So, no, no, no. Don't do that. Don't do
that.
I was uh I was in New York one time. I
was on the subway platform and I saw two
rats uh and they were [__] and I
never saw that before. I'm like, "Holy
[__] there's two rats [__] right
there." And uh so I watched them. Um cuz
you can watch rats [__] It's not a big
deal. You don't have to go.
You can really just totally just watch
them.
Let's see.
Anyway, I'm watching them. I just
curious. I mean, it wasn't surprising
how they do it. It's not like she's on
top going,
thank you. I love it. I love it.
Oh,
>> I think this is a Japanese ride I'm
doing. I don't know.
>> Oh, it's so good to [__] you.
Oh, come on, Ricky. Do me.
All right.
Anyway,
it wasn't anything like that.
It was a pretty standard rat [__] Just
he's on top kind of smooshing her into
the pavement. She's like
And I'm watching them
just I mean I didn't like miss my train
just while I was there
cuz I was I was curious.
That didn't turn me on. I was just
curious cuz I want to know what is it
going to be like when he comes. That's
what I wanted to know. What is it like
when a rat comes? Is it like a is it
just a biological thing? just a
dispassionate kind of just then he just
goes home or is it like [__] yeah it
like
is it you know
is it ecstasy is it an orgasm
and I told that story to a friend of
mine she was like well what about the
girl rat
what about her orgasm
why don't you empower her
and wonder how she comes
What? Are you crazy?
Girl rats don't come. There's no way the
girl gets to come when rats [__] First
of all, he's not going to hold out for
her. He's not that kind of dude. You
could tell. He didn't give a [__] He's
going to [__] her and leave. He doesn't
even know her name. He's not sitting
there waiting for her and trying to
think of things to not come.
Like giant garbage bags with no food in
them or whatever.
And even if he did, she's on a subway
platform in front of people. She's not
going to be able to get to that place,
that inside place that girl rats need
to find their orgasm.
Cuz I know what girl rats need.
I know how to make a girl rat come.
I do. You just pick them up and hold
them upside down and you just
to be clear what I was doing there.
I just want to make sure you know I spin
in her mouth while I played with her
little [__]
Don't judge her. That's what she likes.
I did it for her.
I was watching the Wizard of Oz with my
daughters and uh
I know that's a I know that's a
that's a weird couple of stories to put
together.
fingering a rat's [__] to orgasm and
watching The Wizard of Oz with my
daughters, but they happen to have
happened one right after the other.
Most things that I do I do right after I
made a rat come.
That's what I do at night. It's It's my
It's the only thing I way I I try to
help.
All right.
So,
let me just tell you this first. I was
uh I was at a a place eating dinner in
New York and I heard these two women
talking and one of them is talking about
the guy she's dating. They were about 21
years old, like NYU students. And so,
she's talking about, you know, a lot of
times I hear I'll hear this a woman
talking about the guy she's dating and
she runs down the stuff that's not
satisfying, the things she doesn't like.
She's like, he's just, you know, I text
him and he like doesn't like respond
right away and then when he does like
whatever. So that's weird. And then like
I saw him and he's just being weird. And
and so then he like calls me. He's like
I'm sorry I'm weird cuz it's like weird
right now. And I was like whatever.
It's just weird. And then I'm listening
cuz I want to know what is her friend
going to say. I want to know what kind
of friend she has, you know? And her
friend just says he's a piece of [__]
He's a piece of [__] He's not good
enough for you cuz you're amazing.
You're amazing. So, he just can't handle
how amazing you are. And I remember
thinking, "That is a shitty friend.
That's not a good friend. That is not a
good way to approach life. I'm amazing.
And anybody who doesn't text me back,
it's just can't handle how amazing I am.
I mean, she's a student. She can't be
She's not Nelson Mandela. She's in
college.
She's I'm sure she's fine. But you're
amazing. The way you take classes. What
is What is so amazing? He She's kind of
boring. He's kind of a douche. It's
fine. They're fine.
You need to know that you're boring a
little bit. It's important. Self-love is
a good thing, but self-awareness is more
important. You need to once in a while
go, "I'm kind of an asshole." You have
to have that thought once in a while or
you're a psychopath.
You know, like when you say to a friend
of yours, "You're you're being an
asshole." And they're like, "No, I'm
not." Well, it's not up to you
if you're an [__] or not. That's up
to everybody else.
You don't get to say no to that.
You're an [__] No, I'm not. Oh,
sorry. I thought Okay. I'm glad I
checked. I guess you're not.
If somebody tells you you're you're an
[__] you should go, "Oh, [__] All
right. What happened? How did I get
here?"
It's like somebody saying, "You know,
you got something on your face." No, I
don't.
It's like America. I feel like America
is like the the world's worst
girlfriend. America is like a terrible
girlfriend to the rest of the world. Cuz
when somebody hurts America, she
remembers it forever. But if she does
anything bad, it's like it weds.
It did. I didn't do anything.
America, why do you keep bombing those
people in Yemen and all these go? Cuz
it's 9/11. Okay.
911.
Shut up, [__]
Okay. Well, you killed hundreds of
thousands of people, so I think, yeah,
now. But 9/11. [__] you. You didn't
understand.
Yeah, but you're torturing people. I
did. It wasn't even torture. Oh my god.
He's such a baby. I didn't even do
anything to him.
And I'm saying this about women cuz I'm
a guy. Women might say this about that.
This is what guys like. That's just what
it's like, you know, because I think
racism and sexism are very different. To
me, racism is just a mistake. It's like
just an error. It doesn't really make
any sense. We could just do away with
it. But sexism isn't going anywhere cuz
sexism is way deep the [__] down inside.
So it's just the way we feel about each
other. A women
women
and you're like man man
men man.
Anyway, so I'm watching The Wizard of Oz
with my daughters. Is that enough of a
palette cleanser? All right.
I'm watching The Wizard of Oz. I don't
know if you've seen it. It's about a
little girl named Dorothy.
Uh very sweet little girl played by an
alcoholic older lady who uh
lives in Kansas. She has a dog. She's
very upset
and she keeps telling my dog. And
everybody's like, "This is a farm. We're
working. Leave us alone." And then
there's a tornado. And they all run
inside and they barely look for her.
It's unbelievable. It was so upsetting
to me when I was a kid to see this movie
cuz Auntie's like, "Dorothy." Okay, [__]
it. And she just goes right inside,
bolts the door. Unbelievable.
So Dorothy goes up to Oz. So here's the
thing. I was watching the night. There's
this one moment that really stunned me.
It's when Ray Bulier played the
scarecrow. He he just got ripped apart
by flying monkeys and he's very upset
and he has this performance that's way
over the top even for this movie. Do you
remember that moment the tin man comes
over? What happened? And he's like,
"Well, first they tore my arms off and
they threw them over there
and then they tore my legs off and they
threw them over there."
And I've seen this movie a thousand
times. But for some reason this time,
that moment made me go, "Holy [__]
That was a lot."
And I started to wonder if Victor
Fleming, the guy who directed The Wizard
of Oz, if he had a moment during the
filming of the movie where he was like,
"I think I got to have a word with Ray,
cuz that's getting to be a lot."
All right, let him just let him do
another one.
Okay, action. What happened? Well, first
they tore my arms off and they threw
them over there
and then they tore my legs off and they
threw them over there.
Okay, cut.
Comes over.
Uh,
so listen,
Ray.
Yes.
No, you're fine.
You guys have been great. Thanks a lot
for coming. I hope you enjoyed it. Thank
you very much.
Thank you.
Oh,
happy birthday.